(Leonard:)Almost there.
(Leonard:)- Almost there.
SHELDON: No, we're not.
(Sheldon:)- No, we're not. No, we're not.
- I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)- Watch your fingers.
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Oh, God, my fingers!
- You okay?
- No, it hurt...
(Sheldon:)Great Caesar's ghost, look at this place.
So Penny is a little messy.
(Sheldon:)A little messy?
(Sheldon:)The Mandelbrot set
of complex numbers is a little messy.
(Sheldon:)This is chaos.
(Leonard:)Excuse me.
Explain to me a system...
(Sheldon:)...where a tray of flatware
on a couch is valid?
(Sheldon:)I'm just inferring that this is a couch...
(Sheldon:)...because the evidence suggests
the coffee table's having a tiny garage sale.
Did it occur to you that not everyone
has the compulsive need to sort...
...organize and label
the entire world around them?
(Leonard:)No.
(Leonard:)Well, they don't.
Hard as it may be to believe...